<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-05-10T01:02:18-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/atom.xml</id><title type="html">StayCool21</title><subtitle>CS major @ SIUE</subtitle><author><name>StayCool21</name></author><entry><title type="html">Future Plans</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2024/05/09/future-plans/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Future Plans" /><published>2024-05-09T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2024-05-09T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2024/05/09/future-plans</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2024/05/09/future-plans/"><![CDATA[<p>Even though I’ve completed three years of my coursework going towards my bachelor’s in CS, I ultimately feel like I haven’t been able to develop anything that really excites me. Ultimately, I want to become more involved in web development, as well as utilizing APIs to create some sort of project dealing with F1/NASCAR analytics.</p>

<p>So, here’s my list of the things I hope to accomplish this year, in no particular order…</p>

<ul>
  <li>CAOS Website using Google Firebase
    <ul>
      <li>I really want to get involved with using cloud hosting services with web development, I and one of my college friends will be working to develop our CS club’s website using Firebase as our hosting platform. Other than this portfolio page, this will be my first time developing a full-scale website.</li>
      <li>Hopefully, this will be completed sometime in August 2024.<br /></li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li>Personal Website using AWS
    <ul>
      <li>Just like Firebase, I want to get proficiency in multiple cloud hosting services.</li>
      <li>Site idea: TBD.<br /></li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li>Toying around with the XRP ledger
    <ul>
      <li>I’m no pro at understanding crypto, but it seems like <a href="https://xrpl.org/">XRP</a> will only increase its presence in the market as the world embraces cashless transactions.<br /></li>
    </ul>
  </li>
  <li>Create INDYCAR AI for NR2003 (if I have time…)
    <ul>
      <li>NASCAR Racing 2003 Season, also known as <a href="https://nr2k3.weebly.com/">NR2003</a>, has some of the greatest offline racing AI, which is why it’s still so popular today. However, open-wheel racing physics were never <em>really</em> accessible by the public, as one team of developers made an illegal port of the game that was taken down by the company now known as iRacing (the only other way to race licensed INDYCAR/NASCAR vehicles).</li>
      <li>As I’ve gotten older, I’ve realized that in order to maintain a game as old and good as NR2003, we need to continue to try and make it better. I already have somewhat working single-play <a href="https://github.com/StayCool21/INDYCAR-Edits-for-NR2003">INDYCAR physics</a>, but I want people to be able to enjoy racing with other AI cars.</li>
    </ul>
  </li>
</ul>]]></content><author><name>StayCool21</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even though I’ve completed three years of my coursework going towards my bachelor’s in CS, I ultimately feel like I haven’t been able to develop anything that really excites me. Ultimately, I want to become more involved in web development, as well as utilizing APIs to create some sort of project dealing with F1/NASCAR analytics.]]></summary></entry></feed>